A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 4 FA1296
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 4
1974-1996
Rockefeller Archive Center
FA1296
46 Cubic Feet 115 document boxes
Scope and Contents note
This series contains grant files from 1974 to 1996. It also contains files on the administration and recipients of the John A. and George L. Hartford fellowship program from 1979 to 1986 in Boxes 350 to 361.
Additionally, in 1984, the foundation released a call for applications for up to 12 awards for their five-year Biotechnology Transfer Program. With an annual project budget of $1 million, the foundation sought to provide support to accelerate the technology transfer process among biomedical research projects at the same institution. These files are in Boxes 427 to 428 and 461 to 463.
Biographical/Historical Note
The John A. Hartford Foundation (JAHF) was established in 1929 by brothers John and George Hartford, sons of the founder of the Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company (A&P). The foundation is a private, nonpartisan philanthropy dedicated to improving the care of older adults. For its first several decades, the foundation broadly supported clinical medical research. By 1982, it began to focus solely on geriatric healthcare. In 2015, JAHF paid out $20.2 million on a total of 80 active grants and committed $25.3 million to 24 new grants projects, all focused on the care of older adults.
Immediate Source of Acquisition Note
The John A. Hartford Foundation records were donated to RAC by JAHF in 2014. Record transfers to RAC began in 2014 and continue as needed.
Arrangement Note
Arranged as received
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Other Finding Aids
For Series 1 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA771/collection
For Series 2 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1137/collection
For Series 3 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1218/collection
For Series 5 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1297/collection
For Series 6 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1326/collection
For Series 7 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1138/collection
- Grants, 1974-1996; 4
  - Fellow - Bourdeau, James, 1980 (Box 350, Folder 2684)
  - Fellow - Charleton, Valerie, 1980 (Box 350, Folder 2685)
  - Fellow - Cohen, Richard, 1980 (Box 350, Folder 2686)
  - Fellow - Finberg, Robert, 1980 (Box 350, Folder 2687)
  - Fellow - Hillman, Bruce, 1980 (Box 350, Folder 2688)
  - Fellow - Lorell, Beverly, 1980 (Box 350, Folder 2689)
  - Fellow - Mears, Gregory J., 1980 (Box 351, Folder 2690)
  - Fellow - O'Leary, James J., 1980 (Box 351, Folder 2691)
  - Fellow - Payette, Robert, 1980 (Box 351, Folder 2692)
  - Fellow - Weil, Susan, 1980 (Box 351, Folder 2693)
  - Fellow - Wilson, Christopher, 1980 (Box 351, Folder 2694)
  - Fellow - Zeisel, Steven, 1980 (Box 351, Folder 2695)
  - Fellow - Balin, Arthur, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2696)
  - Fellow - Culpepper, Roy, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2697)
  - Fellow - Gordon, Jeffrey, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2698)
  - Fellow - Harrison, H. Robert, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2699)
  - Fellow - Hoffman, Paul, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2700)
  - Fellow - Horwitz, Marcus, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2701)
  - Fellow - Lipton, Stuart, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2702)
  - Fellow - Luskey, Kenneth, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2703)
  - Fellow - Morrow, Jon, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2704)
  - Fellow - Rankin, J. Scott, 1981 (Box 352, Folder 2705)
  - Fellow - Sondel, Paul, 1981 (Box 353, Folder 2706)
  - Fellow - Weisiger, Richard, 1981 (Box 353, Folder 2707)
  - Fellow - Auerbach, David A., 1983 (Box 353, Folder 2708)
  - Fellow - Chang, Eugene B., 1983 (Box 353, Folder 2709)
  - Fellow - Ganem, Donald E., 1983 (Box 353, Folder 2710)
  - Fellow - Hall, Robert E., 1983 (Box 353, Folder 2711)
  - Fellow - Hoffman, Brian B., 1983 (Box 354, Folder 2712)
  - Fellow - Kauffman, Robert S., 1983 (Box 354, Folder 2713)
  - Fellow - Krontiris, Theodore G., 1983 (Box 354, Folder 2714)
  - Fellow - Laskin, Oscar L., 1983 (Box 354, Folder 2715)
  - Fellow - Liebhaber, Stephen A., 1983 (Box 354, Folder 2716)
  - Fellow - Neubig, Richard R., 1983 (Box 354, Folder 2717)
  - Fellow - Ravdin, Jonathan I., 1983 (Box 354, Folder 2718)
  - Fellow - Schwartz, Bradford S., 1983 (Box 354, Folder 2719)
  - Fellow - Bergey, Gregory, 1984 (Box 355, Folder 2720)
  - Fellow - Choi, Dennis, 1984 (Box 355, Folder 2721)
  - Fellow - Faller, Douglas, 1984 (Box 355, Folder 2722)
  - Fellow - Feinberg, Andrew, 1984 (Box 355, Folder 2723)
  - Fellow - Fleischman, Roger, 1984 (Box 355, Folder 2724)
  - Fellow - Glimcher, Laurie, 1984 (Box 355, Folder 2725)
  - Fellow - Hostetter, Margaret, 1984 (Box 355, Folder 2726)
  - Fellow - Levine, Jon, 1984 (Box 355, Folder 2727)
  - Fellow - Parnes, Jane, 1984 (Box 356, Folder 2728)
  - Fellow - Stanberry, Lawrence, 1984 (Box 356, Folder 2729)
  - Fellow - Storm, Charles, 1984 (Box 356, Folder 2730)
  - Fellow - Victor, Jonathan, 1984 (Box 356, Folder 2731)
  - Fellow - Britt, William, 1985 (Box 356, Folder 2732)
  - Fellow - Brodeur, Garrett M., 1985 (Box 356, Folder 2733)
  - Fellow - Collins, Francis S., 1985 (Box 356, Folder 2734)
  - Fellow - Dailey, Morris, 1985 (Box 356, Folder 2735)
  - Skipped folder number (Box 356, Folder 2736)
  - Fellow - DeBold, C. Rowan, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2737)
  - Fellow - Falk, Ronald, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2738)
  - Fellow - Horwich, Arthur, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2739)
  - Fellow - Lieberburg, Ivan, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2740)
  - Fellow - Lu, Christopher, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2741)
  - Fellow - Mazumder, Amitabha, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2742)
  - Fellow - Moak, Jeffrey, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2743)
  - Fellow - Modlin, Robert, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2744)
  - Fellow - Peroutka, Stephen, 1985 (Box 357, Folder 2745)
  - Fellow - Infante, Anthony, 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2746)
  - Fellow - Kozeny, Gregory, 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2747)
  - Fellow - Kurlan, Roger M., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2748)
  - Fellow - Lee, William, 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2749)
  - Fellow - Leigh, Margaret W., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2750)
  - Fellow - Lowe, John B., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2751)
  - Fellow - Machac, Josef, 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2752)
  - Fellow - Madison, Kathi C., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2753)
  - Fellow - McMillen, Marvin A., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2754)
  - Fellow - Melnick, David A., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2755)
  - Fellow - Meyers, Frederick J., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2756)
  - Fellow - Moench, Thomas R., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2757)
  - Fellow - Pasternack, Gary K., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2758)
  - Fellow - Persing, John A., 1985 (Box 358, Folder 2759)
  - Fellow - Powell, Jerry S., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2760)
  - Fellow - Ramsey, Keith M., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2761)
  - Fellow - Raufman, Jean-Pierre, 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2762)
  - Fellow - Rawhi, Omar A., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2763)
  - Fellow - Reed, Kathryn, L., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2764)
  - Fellow - Reid, Brian J., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2765)
  - Fellow - Rosen, Neal L., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2766)
  - Fellow - Russo, Carlo, 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2767)
  - Fellow - Sharp, Kenneth W., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2768)
  - Fellow - Sherbany, Ariel A., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2769)
  - Fellow - Stein, Leonard A., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2770)
  - Fellow - Stull, Terrence L., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2771)
  - Fellow - Vlock, Daniel R., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2772)
  - Fellow - White, Robert M., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2773)
  - Fellow - Whitley, Patricia N., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2774)
  - Fellow - Willson, James, 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2775)
  - Fellow - Winter, William E., 1985 (Box 359, Folder 2776)
  - Fellow - Ardman, Blair, 1986 (Box 360, Folder 2777)
  - Fellow - Haas, Mark, 1986 (Box 360, Folder 2778)
  - Fellow - Hexem, John, 1986 (Box 360, Folder 2779)
  - Fellow - Kaplan, David, 1986 (Box 360, Folder 2780)
  - Fellow - Marquardt, Diana, 1986 (Box 360, Folder 2781)
  - Fellow - Prystowsky, Michael, 1986 (Box 360, Folder 2782)
  - Fellow - Ratner, Lee, 1986 (Box 360, Folder 2783)
  - Fellow - Schlossman, David, 1986 (Box 360, Folder 2784)
  - Fellow - Udey, Mark, 1986 (Box 361, Folder 2785)
  - Fellow - Yurchenco, Peter, 1986 (Box 361, Folder 2786)
  - Fellowship Press Releases, 1980-1986 (Box 361, Folder 2787)
  - Fellowship Final Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 361, Folder 2788)
  - Fellowship Forms, 1983-1988 (Box 361, Folder 2789)
  - Fellowship Summaries for Board Members, 1982-1985 (Box 361, Folder 2790)
  - JAHF Institutional Grantee Contacts, 1974 (Box 361, Folder 2791)
  - JAHF Grantee Principal Investigators, 1974 (Box 361, Folder 2792)
  - University of Tennessee - A. Rybolt (86-400), 1986-1988 (Box 362, Folder 2793)
  - East Carolina University - E. Furth (86-006), 1986-1988 (Box 362, Folder 2794)
  - Metropolitan Jewish Geriatric Center - D. Kodner (81-418), 1981-1983 (Box 362, Folder 2795-2799)
  - Metropolitan Jewish Geriatric Center - D. Kodner (81-418), 1981-1983 (Box 363, Folder 2800-2802)
  - Metropolitan Jewish Geriatric Center - D. Kodner (82-616), 1982-1984 (Box 363, Folder 2803-2804)
  - Henry Ford Hospital - E. Lewin (84-413), 1984-1988 (Box 363, Folder 2805-2806)
  - Henry Ford Hospital - E. Lewin (84-413), 1984-1988 (Box 364, Folder 2807-2808)
  - Harvard Medical School - S. Goldfinger (83-035), 1983-1986 (Box 364, Folder 2809-2810)
  - Harvard Community Health Plan - D. Berwick (82-621), 1982-1986 (Box 364, Folder 2811-2812)
  - Harvard Community Health Plan - D. Berwick (82-621), 1982-1986 (Box 365, Folder 2813-2814)
  - University of Michicgan - N. Clark (84-101), 1984-1986 (Box 365, Folder 2815-2817)
  - University of Vermont - H. Davis (84-140), 1984-1987 (Box 365, Folder 2818)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation, Project HOPE - J. Iglehart (83-589), 1983-1985 (Box 366, Folder 2819)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation, Project HOPE - J. Iglehart (87-030), 1987-1990 (Box 366, Folder 2820)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation, Project HOPE - J. Iglehart (89-010), 1989-1991 (Box 366, Folder 2821-2822)
  - Institute of Medicine - F. Robbins (84-344), 1984-1987 (Box 366, Folder 2823)
  - Institute of Medicine - F. Robbins (84-344), 1984-1987 (Box 367, Folder 2824)
  - North Carolina Foundation for Alternative Health Programs - J. Bernstein (80-367), 1980-1987 (Box 367, Folder 2825-2829)
  - North Carolina Foundation for Alternative Health Programs - J. Bernstein (80-367), 1980-1987 (Box 368, Folder 2830-2831)
  - Baldwin County (Georgia) Hospital - F. Evans (80-568), 1980-1982 (Box 368, Folder 2832-2833)
  - Baldwin County (Georgia) Hospital - F. Evans (81-419), 1981-1983 (Box 368, Folder 2834)
  - Beloit College - W. Flanigan (80-649), 1980-1983 (Box 368, Folder 2835)
  - Baylor College of Medicine - S. Appel (80-011), 1980-1984 (Box 369, Folder 2836-2838)
  - Baylor College of Medicine - S. Appel (83-011), 1983-1985 (Box 369, Folder 2839)
  - Baylor College of Medicine - R. Demmler (86-007), 1985-1987 (Box 369, Folder 2840-2841)
  - Brown University - D. Greer (80-407), 1980-1983 (Box 370, Folder 2842-2846)
  - Rutgers Medical School, New Jersey College of Medicine and Dentistry - R. Reynolds (79-016), 1979-1982 (Box 371, Folder 2847-2848)
  - Rutgers Medical School, New Jersey College of Medicine and Dentistry - L. Kleinman (80-016), 1980-1983 (Box 371, Folder 2849-2851)
  - Rutgers Medical School, New Jersey College of Medicine and Dentistry - (82-572), 1982-1985 (Box 371, Folder 2852-2853)
  - Safeco, United Healthcare - R. Bond (81-086), 1981-1984 (Box 372, Folder 2854-2857)
  - St. Luke's Hospital - P. Brown (83-220), 1983-1986 (Box 372, Folder 2858-2859)
  - St. Luke's/Roosevelt Hospital - G. Gambuti (80-327), 1980-1983 (Box 373, Folder 2860-2862)
  - Samaritan Health Service - S. Mason (80-010), 1980-1981 (Box 373, Folder 2863)
  - University of Arizona - J. Christianson (82-476), 1982-1984 (Box 373, Folder 2864-2865)
  - University of Arizona - J. Christianson (82-476), 1982-1984 (Box 374, Folder 2866-2867)
  - United Health Services - L. Battaglini (81-147), 1981-1983 (Box 374, Folder 2868-2870)
  - United Health Services - L. Battaglini (82-679), 1982-1984 (Box 374, Folder 2871-2872)
  - United Health Services - L. Battaglini (82-679), 1982-1984 (Box 375, Folder 2873)
  - University at Buffalo Foundation - C. Nowak (83-109), 1983-1985 (Box 375, Folder 2874-2877)
  - South Florida Health Action Coalition - J. Erb (80-461), 1980-1984 (Box 376, Folder 2878-2880)
  - National Executive Service Corps - D. Clark (81-263), 1981-1983 (Box 376, Folder 2881-2883)
  - National Executive Service Corps - D. Clark (81-263), 1981-1983 (Box 377, Folder 2884-2885)
  - National Hospice Organization - J. Magno (80-407), 1980-1981 (Box 377, Folder 2886-2888)
  - New York Business Group on Health - L. Warshaw (81-243), 1981-1983 (Box 377, Folder 2889-2890)
  - New York Philharmonic - K. Ockenden (84-252) (Box 378, Folder 2891)
  - New York Community Trust Energy Conservation Fund - C. Miller (81-337), 1981-1987 (Box 378, Folder 2892-2894)
  - Brown University, National Hospice Study - D. Greer (80-407), 1980-1984 (Box 378, Folder 2895-2896)
  - Brown University, National Hospice Study - D. Greer (80-407), 1980-1984 (Box 379, Folder 2897)
  - Indochinese Cultural and Service Center - C. Law (82-535), 1982-1985 (Box 379, Folder 2898-2899)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association - D. Stern (83-127), 1983-1986 (Box 379, Folder 2900-2902)
  - Lincoln Center Institute - J. Mazzola (81-252), 1981-1984 (Box 380, Folder 2903)
  - Luthor Medical Center - G. Adams (83-323), 1983-1985 (Box 380, Folder 2904)
  - Manhattan Eye, Ear, and Throat Hospital - W. Renchard (81-176), 1981-1983 (Box 380, Folder 2905-2906)
  - Alameda Health Consortium - H. Smith (81-051), 1981-1982 (Box 380, Folder 2907)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - A. Mulley (80-293), 1980-1984 (Box 381, Folder 2908-2909)
  - Amagin, Inc. - R. Chitester (80-633), 1980-1984 (Box 381, Folder 2910-2911)
  - Amagin, Inc. - R. Chitester (82-633), 1982-1984 (Box 381, Folder 2912)
  - Amagin, Inc. - R. Chitester (82-633), 1982-1984 (Box 382, Folder 2913)
  - American College of Physicians - S. Schwartz (80-304), 1980-1984 (Box 382, Folder 2914-2918)
  - American College of Physicians - S. Schwartz (80-304), 1980-1984 (Box 383, Folder 2919)
  - American Enterprise Institute - J. Meyer (81-055), 1981-1983 (Box 383, Folder 2920-2924)
  - Choate-Symmes Health Service - T. Heubner (83-119), 1983-1986 (Box 384, Folder 2925-2927)
  - Commonwealth Health Care Corporation - R. Spence (82-546), 1981-1983 (Box 384, Folder 2928-2930)
  - Commonwealth Health Care Corporation - R. Spence (82-546), 1981-1983 (Box 385, Folder 2931)
  - Executive Service Corps - M. Berz (82-632), 1982-1985 (Box 385, Folder 2932)
  - Executive Service Corps - M. Berz (83-183), 1983-1985 (Box 385, Folder 2933)
  - Eskaton Administrative Center - R. Wexler (80-409), 1980-1981 (Box 385, Folder 2934)
  - Georgetown University - J. Reuter (80-301), 1980-1985 (Box 385, Folder 2935)
  - Georgetown University - J. Reuter (80-301), 1980-1985 (Box 386, Folder 2936-2937)
  - Hospice of Santa Barbara - C. Zimmer (84-228), 1982-1984 (Box 386, Folder 2938-2939)
  - University of Connecticut - R. Lusky (83-292), 1983-1986 (Box 386, Folder 2940-2941)
  - University of Connecticut - R. Lusky (83-292), 1983-1986 (Box 387, Folder 2942)
  - University of Illinois - G. Winsberg (82-582) (Box 387, Folder 2943)
  - Utah Health Cost Management Foundation - P. Singer (79-190), 1979-1983 (Box 387, Folder 2944-2946)
  - Utah Health Cost Management Foundation - P. Singer (82-190), 1982-1984 (Box 387, Folder 2947)
  - Utah Health Cost Management Foundation - P. Singer (82-190), 1982-1984 (Box 388, Folder 2948-2950)
  - Waveny Care Center - K. Hannan (83-318), 1983-1985 (Box 388, Folder 2951)
  - Wilmer Ophthalmological Institute, Johns Hopkins - A. Patz (80-644), 1980-1982 (Box 388, Folder 2952)
  - Yale University - J. Binder (76-186), 1976-1987 (Box 389, Folder 2953-2955)
  - Alliance to Save Energy - J. Wolf (no grant number), 1985-1988 (Box 389, Folder 2956)
  - Northern Sierra Hospital Council - D. Ogburn (79-017), 1979-1981 (Box 389, Folder 2957)
  - Northern Sierra Hospital Council - S. Avery (80-017), 1980-1983 (Box 389, Folder 2958-2960)
  - Northern Sierra Hospital Council - S. Avery (83-083), 1983-1985 (Box 390, Folder 2961-2965)
  - Ohio State University - C. Kunin (80-563), 1980-1984 (Box 390, Folder 2966)
  - Ohio State University - C. Kunin (80-563), 1980-1984 (Box 391, Folder 2967)
  - Ohio State University - C. Kunin (82-604), 1982-1983 (Box 391, Folder 2968-2970)
  - Omaha Cost Containment Coalition - J. Johnson (81-247), 1981-1984 (Box 391, Folder 2971)
  - Omaha Cost Containment Coalition - J. Johnson (81-247), 1981-1984 (Box 392, Folder 2972-2974)
  - Providence Medical Center - M. Schreiber (81-006), 1981-1983 (Box 392, Folder 2975-2977)
  - San Bernadino Primary Care Health Care System - T. Louie (81-068 ), 1981-1984 (Box 393, Folder 2978-2981)
  - Faculty for Continuing Medical Education - M. Horwith (84-067), 1984-1986 (Box 393, Folder 2982-2983)
  - Faculty for Continuing Medical Education - M. Horwith (84-067), 1984-1986 (Box 394, Folder 2984-2986)
  - University of California, San Franciscio - S. Schroeder (80-255), 1980-1984 (Box 394, Folder 2987-2988)
  - University of California, San Francisco - A. Martin (83-271), 1983-1986 (Box 394, Folder 2989)
  - Cooper Union Research Foundation - L. Nattress (84-424), 1984-1987 (Box 395, Folder 2990-2992)
  - County of Santa Barbara (CA) Health Care Services - L. Hart (80-468), 1980-1983 (Box 395, Folder 2993-2995)
  - County of Santa Barbara Health Care Services - (82-552), 1982-1984 (Box 396, Folder 2996-2999)
  - East Harlem Council for Human Services - Y. Sanchez (80-294), 1980-1983 (Box 396, Folder 3000-3001)
  - East Harlem Council for Human Services - Y. Sanchez (80-294), 1980-1983 (Box 397, Folder 3002-3003)
  - Maternity Center Association - R. Lubic (81-040), 1981-1983 (Box 397, Folder 3004-3005)
  - Maternity Center Association - R. Lubic (83-016), 1983-1985 (Box 397, Folder 3006)
  - Maternity Center Association - R. Lubic (83-016), 1983-1985 (Box 398, Folder 3007-3012)
  - Maternity Center Association - R. Lubic (85-126), 1985-1987 (Box 399, Folder 3013)
  - Monterey County (CA) Department of Health - D. DuBois (80-592), 1980-1983 (Box 399, Folder 3014-3015)
  - Monterey County (CA) Department of Health - L. Zimmerman (83-028), 1983-1984 (Box 399, Folder 3016)
  - National Institute on Aging - T. Williams (85-114), 1985-1986 (Box 399, Folder 3017)
  - New York Regional Association of Grant Makers - J. Coleman (no grant number), 1978-1980 (Box 399, Folder 3018)
  - New York Regional Association of Grant Makers - J. Coleman (no grant number), 1978-1980 (Box 400, Folder 3019)
  - Overlook Hospital - R. Averill (81-146), 1981-1986 (Box 400, Folder 3020-3024)
  - Philadelphia Geriatric Center - E. Brody (83-069), 1983-1985 (Box 401, Folder 3025-3027)
  - Philadelphia Geriatric Center - E. Brody (85-094), 1985-1987 (Box 401, Folder 3028-3031)
  - Philadelphia Geriatric Center - E. Brody (85-094), 1985-1987 (Box 402, Folder 3032-3033)
  - Brookings Institution - A. Rivlin (84-241), 1984-1988 (Box 402, Folder 3034-3036)
  - Brookings Institution - A. Rivlin (84-241), 1984-1988 (Box 403, Folder 3037)
  - Clackamas Health Care Consortium - L. Weidel (81-160), 1981-1983 (Box 403, Folder 3038-3039)
  - Clackamas Health Care Consortium - (82-590), 1982-1985 (Box 403, Folder 3040-3041)
  - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center - D. Ginsberg (80-406), 1980-1983 (Box 403, Folder 3042)
  - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center - D. Ginsberg (80-406), 1980-1983 (Box 404, Folder 3043-3044)
  - Columbia University School of Medicine - J. Benvenuto (82-534), 1982-1984 (Box 404, Folder 3045)
  - Community Services Society of New York - M. Clark (80-451), 1980-1983 (Box 404, Folder 3046-3047)
  - Community Services Society of New York - B. Beck (82-668), 1982-1986 (Box 404, Folder 3048)
  - Community Services Society of New York - B. Beck (82-668), 1982-1986 (Box 405, Folder 3049)
  - Yale University - D. Lensing (80-304), 1980-1982 (Box 405, Folder 3050)
  - Yale University - D. Lensing (81-341), 1981-1983 (Box 405, Folder 3051)
  - Yale University - D. Lensing (82-341), 1982-1984 (Box 405, Folder 3052)
  - Yale Medical School - D. Brand/L. Goldman (83-102), 1983-1985 (Box 405, Folder 3053)
  - Yale Medical School - D. Brand/L. Goldman (83-102), 1983-1985 (Box 406, Folder 3054-3056)
  - Yale University - D. Brand (84-438), 1984-1986 (Box 406, Folder 3057-3059)
  - Yale University - D. Brand (85-217), 1985-1988 (Box 406, Folder 3060)
  - Yale University - D. Brand (85-217), 1985-1988 (Box 407, Folder 3061-3066)
  - InterStudy - W. McClure (79-022), 1979-1981 (Box 408, Folder 3067)
  - InterStudy - R. Olson (80-300), 1980-1984 (Box 408, Folder 3068-3072)
  - InterStudy - R. Olson (80-300), 1980-1984 (Box 409, Folder 3073-3075)
  - InterStudy - P. Ellwood (83-178), 1983-1986 (Box 409, Folder 3076-3078)
  - InterStudy - P. Ellwood (83-178), 1983-1986 (Box 410, Folder 3079-3084)
  - InterStudy - P. Ellwood (83-178), 1983-1986 (Box 411, Folder 3085)
  - InterStudy - C. Polich (86-285), 1986-1989 (Box 411, Folder 3086-3091)
  - InterStudy - C. Polich (86-285), 1986-1989 (Box 412, Folder 3092-3098)
  - InterStudy - C. Polich (86-285), 1986-1989 (Box 413, Folder 3099-3101)
  - InterStudy - P. Ellwood (86-376), 1986-1987 (Box 413, Folder 3102)
  - Johns Hopkins University - C. Schramm (79-012), 1979-1981 (Box 413, Folder 3103-3104)
  - Johns Hopkins University - C. Schramm (80-012), 1980-1984 (Box 414, Folder 3105-3109)
  - Johns Hopkins University - C. Schramm (80-012), 1980-1984 (Box 415, Folder 3110-3111)
  - Johns Hopkins University - C. Schramm (82-556), 1982-1986 (Box 415, Folder 3112-3115)
  - Johns Hopkins University - C. Schramm (82-556), 1982-1986 (Box 416, Folder 3116-3118)
  - Johns Hopkins University - C. Schramm (85-215), 1985-1989 (Box 416, Folder 3119-3121)
  - New York Hospital/Cornell Medical Center - E. McCarthy (81-305), 1981-1985 (Box 417, Folder 3122-3124)
  - New York Hospital - M. Sniffen (84-087), 1984-1985 (Box 417, Folder 3125-3127)
  - New York Hospital - D. Thompson (84-471), 1984-1987 (Box 417, Folder 3128)
  - New York Hospital - D. Thompson (84-471), 1984-1987 (Box 418, Folder 3129-3135)
  - Presbyterian Homes Inc. - K. Holstein (87-031), 1987-1989 (Box 419, Folder 3136-3138)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation, Project HOPE - G. Wilensky (84-072), 1984-1988 (Box 419, Folder 3139-3141)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation, Project HOPE - G. Wilensky (84-072), 1984-1988 (Box 420, Folder 3142-3143)
  - University of Pennsylvania - J. Schwartz (84-485), 1984-1989 (Box 420, Folder 3144-3146)
  - University of Washington/King County Department of Health - C. Wood (79-028), 1979-1983 (Box 420, Folder 3147)
  - University of Washington/King County Department of Health - C. Wood (79-028), 1979-1983 (Box 421, Folder 3148-3149)
  - University of Washington - R. Tompkins (80-028), 1980-1983 (Box 421, Folder 3150)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - University of Colorado - L. Robbins (84-377), 1984-1986 (Box 421, Folder 3151)
  - Mid-Career Fellow - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine - R. Butler (84-380), 1984-1986 (Box 421, Folder 3152)